Vod2smi by Blue-Bird™
What is this place?
My life doesn't really make sense.
Hey.
Oh...
I used to ask myself
a lot of questions
about that.
"Scott, you're a divorced ex-con.
"How are you an Avenger?
"Why are you time traveling
with Captain America?
"That doesn't make sense."
A lot has changed about my life.
But everywhere I go,
people ask me the same thing.
Can you take a picture with my dog?
"Scott, what about now?"
"What's next?"
"Where does the ride take you?"
If I knew that,
it wouldn't be a ride.
All right.
It's been a crazy few years.
Hey, guys.
Hey, hi. How are you?
For everyone.
Everything is ready for you.
You're too much.
No, no, no.
Your money's no good here.
Aw.
Are we still talking about that?
Yes, of course.
Rubin, you are the best.
Thank you, Spider-Man.
So, let's make time for
the stuff that really matters.
Like friends.
Friends you didn't even know you had.
Remember the people who got you here.
You couldn't have done it without them.
Hey, I'm just a guy who
got fired from Baskin-Robbins.
Sometimes you just get lucky.
I'm lucky I met Hope Van Dyne.
I think you know who she is.
She's taken back her dad's company.
Now she's using the Pym Particle
for global change.
A lot of people say they want
to save the world,
but Hope, she saves it every day.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Reforestation.
Affordable housing.
Food production.
She's not wasting a second.
I still can't believe it.
None of this should have happened.
But it did.
It's a pretty good world.
I'm glad we saved it.
"Do I miss the action?
"Sometimes."
"Will I be there when the Avengers need me?
"Absolutely.
"I'd never turn my back on them.
"But right now, the only job
I want is being a dad.
"I love you, Cassie.
"Thanks for being my hero.
"And I'm sorry I missed some birthdays."
"And for the rest of you kids out there,
"word of advice.
"Look out for the little guy.
"Make mistakes.
"Take chances.
"Because if there's one thing
life's taught me,
"there's always room to grow."
Sorry, that's me.
Why is jail calling?
Lang!
I'm here.
All right, come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey. Is she okay?
Have you heard anything?
Not yet. No. Oh.
Hi, Hope.
Hey, Dad.
Cassie.
What happened?
Sign here.
Oh, you know, just jail stuff.
Give it back.
Hmm?
I know it was you.
Are you sure?
I mean, it was kind of hard to see
through all that tear gas
you fired into the park
full of peaceful protestors.
Where is it?
I'm sorry. This must be
really embarrassing for you.
Oh!
I did find this though.
You shrank a cop car?
What were you thinking?
What was I supposed to do?
Look the other way?
They were clearing out a homeless camp
in the middle of the night.
No, I'm not saying that...
And where do
they expect them to go?
It's not their fault that they
lost their homes in the Blip.
I... I know that.
No one can even afford rent right now,
unless you're some trust-fund asshole.
I'm not telling you what to do.
I'm just saying...
Telling her what to do.
Telling me exactly what to do.
No, you do what you want.
I'm suggesting another way to do it.
Okay.
You know, I promised your mom
that you would only use this stuff
when one of us was around.
It's really dangerous tech.
I know it's dangerous.
What if the cops took it from you? Huh?
What if you lost it?
I didn't lose the suit.
You have a suit?
Wait, you have a suit?
I know how to take care of myself, okay?
Trust me.
I'm pretty good at it by now.
Ouch.
I didn't mean it like that.
I know.
I'm sorry.
That's okay. It's all right.
I get it.
I just think you should get
to have a normal life.
Dad, a guy dressed like a bee
tried to kill me in my room
when I was six.
I've never had a normal life.
How about some music?
"And in that moment,
"all I could think was,
"'How did the Hulk
turn me into a baby?
"'Will I be a baby forever?
"'Am I the Hulk's baby?'"
Dad, are you listening to your own book?
"But I was ready for anything."
Hmm? No, that's, uh...
It's just the radio.
"Steve and I
grew close over that."
- Dad, turn it off.
- It's so weird.
Something's wrong with this switch.
It won't turn off.
I said turn it off.
What's that? Turn it up?
All right.
"A little after that,
"a raccoon from space showed up.
"I don't think he knew my name.
"I was just happy to meet
a raccoon who could talk."
Mm.
Excuse me.
Oh.
Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
All right.
Your Nobel Prize is in the mail.
It better be.
I just saved eight bucks.
God, I admire you.
Thank you.
I missed this.
No pizza in the Quantum Realm?
No. No anything.
You know, Mom,
you can talk about it.
If you want.
Sweetheart, I spent 30 years down there.
I wanna live right now.
Yep.
So, Cassie, did you make any new friends
in the slammer this time?
Grandpa.
"This time"?
Was there a last time?
I mean, last time barely counts.
I didn't know that.
Why didn't you call me?
'Cause I knew you'd be like this.
I would've just broken you out with ants.
All right, you know what?
Family meeting.
Can we have a family meeting?
Isn't that what we're doing?
Yeah, I mean about this.
About everybody being so fine with this.
Look, you wanna help.
I get it.
I do, Cassie. I really do.
But I don't want you wasting your life.
At least I'm still trying
to do something with mine.
I literally saved the world.
Oh, did you?
Well, yeah, you never
mentioned that before.
Hey, everybody,
Scott saved the world.
How was that for you, Scott?
You should write a book about it.
Ha ha.
Hilarious.
Yeah, you're welcome
for all not being dust.
And what do you do now?
Sign books?
Aren't you the guy
who broke into VistaCorp?
Aren't you the guy who flew
all the way to Germany
just to fight Captain America
at the airport?
Fight with Captain America
at the airport.
Wouldn't fight Captain America.
Not insane.
People still need help, Dad.
At least we're trying
to do something that matters.
Who's "we"?
Hmm?
What are you three up to?
Science.
With ants.
Ant science.
I don't believe you.
Let's just show him.
Whoa.
What are they building?
Are you doing this?
Actually, no,
they built their own tech.
Pretty smart ants.
Okay, so when you were all,
like, gone those five years,
I had a lot of time.
And I started reading
Grandpa Hank's old journals,
and I got really into
the Quantum Realm and...
Whoa.
The Quantum Realm?
I know we all have a history there,
and I didn't want to freak anyone out,
but we've been talking about it.
She had some questions, okay?
I can't help if people
are inspired by me.
So, you've been studying
the Quantum Realm?
Mm-hmm.
Why didn't you ask me about it?
I tried, Mom.
A lot.
You never wanted to talk about it.
Cassie's just been curious
and we gave her some pointers.
This isn't exactly
ant science, is it, Henry?
You know how dangerous
the Quantum Realm is.
Yeah, we all do, Mom.
Nobody's going to the Quantum Realm.
That's why we made this.
It's like a satellite
for deep space or the ocean.
But...
...Quantum.
We just need a map.
And then we can study
and explore
the entire Quantum Realm.
Never even have to go.
Your daughter built
a subatomic Hubble Telescope
in a basement.
You know,
if I had something like this
when you were gone...
then I could have found you.
It's amazing.
I'm blown away.
How does it work?
It's kinda like that
two-way radio we used to have.
You send a signal down from here,
and then it collects the data,
and it sends it back.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
You're sending a signal
down to the Quantum Realm?
Yeah.
Shut it down now.
Janet...
Why would we shut it...
What's wrong?
You have to turn it off!
Stop and tell us what's wrong!
Janet?
There's something I should have told...
Dad?
No!
Mom!
Damn it!
Dad?
Dad!
Cassie.
Oh, Dad. Come on.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Where are we?
Mom!
Dad!
Hope. Over here.
Are you okay?
We should be dead.
Why aren't we?
I don't know.
Are we where I think we are?
I would say yes,
but, uh, it wasn't like this.
Janet!
Mom!
Do not move.
We need to find Scott and Cassie.
Right now.
Hope?
Hank?
Can you hear me?
Can anyone hear me?
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
What are we gonna do?
It's okay. It's okay.
We're okay.
It's gonna be okay.
You're saying "okay" too much.
Okay. All right. Okay.
Well, it's 'cause we are.
We're okay.
We are fine.
Hey, we're gonna find them,
and we're gonna go home.
Mm.
In the meantime, look around.
It's beautiful.
All right?
We're outside.
It's like we're camping.
We love camping.
We've never been camping.
But we've always talked about it.
Is that sun moving?
Get back!
Oh, my God.
I don't think this is a sun!
It's fine.
- Dad!
- Honey, it's okay.
Still okay.
Dad.
Oh, my God.
That was weird.
Run.
There's Quantum people in the Quantum Realm?
Yeah.
I didn't know that either.
What was that back there, Mom?
What was that ship looking for?
Keep your voice down.
You said there was nothing down here.
Why didn't you tell us about all of this?
Hope, I will explain everything,
but right now,
I just need you to trust me.
Then make me trust you!
Let's just calm down, all right?
We can talk about this...
We don't have time to talk, Henry.
No, you need to tell us what's...
And why didn't you listen?
I told you to stay away from here.
Janet, I... I'm so sorry.
I should have told you what we were doing.
I had no idea...
I know.
It's...
We'll talk later.
Right now, we stick together,
we find Scott and Cassie,
and we go home.
Okay?
Okay.
Stay close.
This is incredible.
I've studied the Quantum Realm for years.
Why didn't I see any of this?
You weren't able to look deep enough.
Not through the Void and Subatomica.
There are worlds here,
worlds within worlds.
It's a place outside time and space.
It's a secret universe
beneath ours.
Hey, get your hands off me!
Cassie?
Where's my daughter?
Where is she?
Cassie?
Where's my daughter?
Cassie!
Dad!
Drink the ooze.
What?
I'll handle this.
Mom.
Was that a... a good stab?
I got us a ride.
He's friendly.
Quite a ride.
Says the man who invented
flying on the back of an ant.
I like ants.
And I love that you love them.
Here.
These will help us blend in.
Where exactly are we going on this?
We're not too far
from an old friend of mine.
If anyone's heard
where Scott and Cassie are,
it'll be him.
After you.
Saddle up, Ant-Man.
Let me go!
I don't know what you're saying!
I don't know what you...
No!
Drink the ooze!
Hello.
Whoa!
Hi.
Did you drink the ooze?
Why can I understand you?
Oh. Great.
That's the ooze.
Hey, everybody, it worked!
Ooze worked!
We can finally be friends.
Hi. I am Veb.
You just drank me.
I did... What?
Oh. Do you need some more ooze?
Here.
I can pour some ooze into your hole...
No, I'm okay.
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Oh, wow!
A big hole.
How many holes do you have?
I'm sorry.
Is that a personal question?
I don't have any holes.
His name is Scott Lang.
He has seven holes.
Yeah, that's right.
How did you...
How did you know that?
He's Quaz.
He's a telepath.
You can read minds?
Yeah, and I really wish I couldn't.
Everyone is disgusting.
Hmm.
Could you please stop thinking that?
Sorry.
Please, stop.
Thinking?
Thinking that.
I'm trying.
Well, not very hard.
And I think you look weird too.
I don't think you look weird.
I think you look really cool.
I wish my head glowed.
No, no, you don't.
I know I don't. I just...
I'm nervous, okay?
And it just came out.
What are you doing here?
Are you a spy?
What? No. No, no.
We should torture him.
Guys.
No, it's okay.
We're not... We're not spies.
He's my dad.
Oh!
Oh... Thank you.
Welcome.
Then who is San Francisco?
It's where we're from.
It's a place.
Then what's Earth?
It's also where we're from.
We should torture them.
Why are you always
trying to torture people?
We have other options.
Do things come out of your holes,
like milk, juice...
Veb, stop asking about his holes.
Some of us have holes.
What are you doing here?
Where are you from?
Okay.
Up there. Up there.
See, above this...
The Earth.
...it's a different universe.
Big Earth.
It's the same universe,
but it's bigger.
This is Earth,
but it's a very small Earth.
- Sometimes, I guess.
- I get big. I shrink.
And it's like...
But I wrote a book about it, actually.
- I don't know.
- This is the Quantum Realm.
You have to shrink to
get in the Quantum Realm.
We shrunk.
Right now, we're really small.
It's bigger where we're from.
So, we're small right now.
It's bigger.
Okay, they're telling the truth.
It doesn't matter.
You come from above.
Like him.
So, he is hunting you.
He will burn the world to find you.
Who?
The Conqueror.
There are beings down here.
Intelligent beings.
I always theorized it was possible,
but to be here,
a subatomic universe.
This changes everything
we know about life,
evolution, our place in the galaxy...
Holy shit!
That guy looks like broccoli.
Keep your head down.
Follow me.
Drink those.
I'll be right back.
I'm here for Krylar.
Oh.
It's... It's you.
Let's keep that between us.
And Krylar.
Hello.
I don't know your ways or customs,
but I assume that you have a beverage
that can get me drunk?
Absolutely, sir.
Hmm.
So, what's your story then?
God.
Move.
It's time.
Follow me.
Right this way.
Hmm.
Oh.
How exactly do you know this guy?
Old, uh, freedom fighter friend of mine.
Sorry, you were a freedom fighter?
Or terrorist.
Depends on who you ask.
But, trust me, he can help.
Janet Van Dyne?
I thought you were dead.
Been a long time, Krylar.
Officially, Lord Krylar now.
I fought like hell against that.
It sounds so elitist.
You have got to be Hank.
I've heard so much
about you and your ants.
What are ants anyway?
Do we have 'em down here?
I don't think so.
No.
Oh. That's too bad.
Hope.
You have to be Hope.
She talked about you every day.
That's strange,
she never said anything about you.
I don't think I would have
told my kid either.
Wild stuff.
Funny.
Hmm.
How wild?
Very wild, Henry.
Yeah.
Uh...
Krylar, we need your help.
Janet, after all
we've been through, together,
just ask me.
Tell me, how can I help?
But...
is anyone starving?
I'm starving.
Boys...
Now.
They don't know anything.
About... anything.
Then get them out of here.
Excuse me.
Look, he's right.
I don't know what's going on.
We're just trying to find our family.
Do you have a map?
All we wanna do is go... Whoa!
Wait, wait.
Don't shoot.
They're with us.
Is that building alive?
Yours are dead?
Look. Excuse me.
We just wanna go home.
At least you still have a home.
What happened here?
The Conqueror burned our homes.
Our stories.
He built his citadel
on the bones of our people.
Some of us escaped,
found others on the run.
We gathered who we could to fight.
It was never enough.
I'm sorry.
We can help.
Uh, Cassie...
Dad, you're an Avenger.
They need help.
No. What I need to do is get you home.
Why don't you wanna help?
We don't know anything about this place.
I mean, I don't even know
how time works down here.
Have we been gone for 10 seconds?
Or have we been gone for 10 years?
Think about your mom right now.
Can you imagine what she must be...
Don't use Mom as an excuse.
You just don't care.
No, I do care.
I know you wanna help.
I do.
But this is not our fight.
Just 'cause it's not happening to you,
doesn't mean it's not happening.
Hey.
Would you look at me?
She's disappointed in you.
I got that. Yeah. Thank you.
You're welcome.
We'll talk about it later.
Right now, let's just find the others.
No one knows this place better than Janet.
What did you say?
What?
That name.
Janet Van Dyne.
Where is she?
That's what we're trying to find out.
You know her?
I know her.
She shouldn't be here.
Hey, bring a round
of the chasers, please.
Yes, thank you.
If you haven't had this,
don't try it
unless you want to change your life.
Mmm.
Krylar, we're looking for friends of ours.
Two of them.
Human, like us.
Human, that's the word.
Totally forgot what you call
yourselves up there.
Human.
Are you not human?
Not technically, but yes.
In the ways that matter.
No!
Let us talk.
So, what is it that brings you to us, Janet?
If I remember correctly, you left.
You left all of us.
With him.
Janet, what is he talking about?
You didn't tell them about him.
Did you say anything
about what you did here?
How many people died because of you?
Does your family even know who you are?
Your mommy
is full of secrets.
You're lying.
I lie.
A lot.
Not about this.
Let them go.
He just wants me.
But you want them.
So they're coming too.
Along with those other friends of yours.
I heard about them.
But he did too.
And, uh, he sent the Hunter.
What kind of hunter?
Uh, not a man.
Not a machine.
A mechanized organism designed only
for killing.
Where are they?
No clue.
Dead.
Probably dead.
Oh, this is so sad when all of this
could have been avoided, Janet.
Just give him what he wants.
What happened to you?
We fought against him.
He can be very persuasive.
Let's pay him a visit.
I think we're done here.
Can that ship get us out of here?
Cover me?
Always.
Henry, take the helm.
I'm gonna hot-wire this thing.
Where are the controls?
Those are the controls.
What the hell?
You'll be great.
It's like flying a bike.
Is the bike alive?
Hands, all the way in!
Like stuffing a turkey.
Ugh.
Really, him?
He used to be charming.
That guy?
I was down here for 30 years, Henry.
I had needs.
Oh, my God.
Look, I get it.
I've got needs too.
Oh, my God!
I had dinner with someone a few times.
Her name was Linda.
It didn't work out.
What went wrong?
She wasn't you, baby.
Get everyone in the ships.
We're leaving.
All right.
- And, Xolum.
- Right here.
Take them as far away from here as you can.
Why?
What?
If you're looking for Janet,
he's looking for you.
You led them straight to us.
Come on, come on.
Take as many as you can.
We'll hold them off.
Go!
Come on!
Hurry, hurry!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
Get on.
Get on now!
We have to go now.
Now!
Oh, my God!
Cassie, let's go!
Get to the sanctuary.
Wait for my message.
- Veb, we're leaving.
- No. No, wait!
- Move! Move!
- All my friends.
Give up the travelers.
The Conqueror will show you mercy.
I know his mercy.
Stay here.
I'm...
Cassie?
Oh, no.
Okay.
I have a suit.
Yeah, I noticed.
You okay?
Yes.
Look, momentum, right?
Jump, tap, right?
One move. Jump, tap.
I know how to do it, Dad.
- Oh, do you? Really?
- Yes.
'Cause it didn't look like it from my end.
I just... I messed up on the timing.
Jump...
Like that.
You see what I did?
No.
You're like this small.
I jumped and tapped.
Jentorra, we have to go.
Get to the ship!
Welcome back
to the Quantum Realm, Scott.
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
What?
Is someone in there?
Oh, yes.
The destiny you cannot escape.
Our fates have always
been forged together...
ever since that day we met.
Wow.
Scott Lang.
Get away from us!
The day you broke me.
- Banished me down here.
- Wait.
Darren?
Surprised to see me?
Yeah.
It's the bee guy?
- It's the bee guy?
- Cassie?
I almost didn't recognize you.
How are you not dead?
I became the ultimate weapon.
That... That...
That's what this is?
Look, Darren.
Darren is dead!
There is only M.O.D.O.K.!
And there's no place you can run, Scott.
Not from me.
And not from him.
He's the future.
He's the past.
And now all he needs is you.
Mom?
What's after Scott and Cassie?
We have to find them.
There's something I have to do first.
They could be dead!
Hope, please.
And you're still hiding things from us.
I am trying to protect you.
From what?
Who are you so afraid of?
Third time in jail?
Four.
And here we are again.
Face to face.
That's a face.
It's a...
It's a big face.
Why are you just a floating head?
Maybe you could
walk us through this, Darren.
You left Darren to die
in the Quantum Realm.
But the Conqueror found me.
Rebuilt me.
Made me the ultimate weapon.
A mechanized organism
designed only for...
Oh, M.O.D.O.K.?
Oh, uh, MO... Oh, I get it.
It's an acronym.
Mechanized organism designed only for killing.
Actually, that's M.O.D.O.F.K.
I bet you thought
you'd seen the last of me.
Just now noticing the baby legs.
They're not baby legs.
A little bit like a Bjorn.
You think you're so smart.
Scott Lang, the man
who took everything from me.
Who stole my whole life.
But I did it.
I got you here.
I found your signal, Cassie.
Thanks for that, by the way.
Couldn't have done it without you.
You're looking at a man set free.
I've created so much more here
than you could possibly imagine.
All for him.
I wasn't the only one stranded
in the Quantum Realm.
What is this place?
He said he was a traveler.
A scientist who crashed off course.
He had a ship
beyond anything I had ever seen.
A ship that could travel the Multiverse.
The Multiverse?
As in alternate dimensions?
Parallel realities?
I didn't believe it at first.
But it's real.
Just like we theorized.
Can this take us home?
It can take you anywhere.
Yah!
I'd never met anyone like him.
He felt so
lost.
I guess we both were.
But we had a way out.
We tried everything
to recharge his ship's energy core.
Nothing worked.
But after so many years alone,
it was nice to have a friend.
I lied to Hope.
I told her I was coming home.
I can see her by the door.
Waiting for me.
That's the last thing I did...
was lie to her.
I just thought I'd have more time.
I can give that to you.
Time.
It's not what you think it is.
It's a cage.
And it does everything it can
to break you.
It's not until you free
yourself from it that you see
just how small
it always was.
We're going to get out of here.
She's gonna open the door...
...and you'll be there.
I promise.
Let's get to work.
Okay.
It took ages,
but we did it.
We brought it back to life.
Let's go home.
His ship was neurokinetic.
Connected to his thoughts.
When I touched it...
I saw his mind.
I felt...
...what he had done.
Entire worlds,
entire timelines.
Gone, like they never even existed.
Janet?
We can leave.
Right now.
Who is Kang?
Who I need to be.
He didn't crash here.
He was exiled here.
Outside space and time.
The only place
that could hold him.
Exiled?
By who?
I don't know.
But they sabotaged his ship.
And trapped him here.
And because of me,
he was getting out.
Janet?
Stay away.
You saved my life.
I made a promise.
Just let me take you home.
And then?
What are you going to do?
Win.
I told you time isn't what you think.
I can make it...
so you never left her.
Hope is going to open the door
and you'll be there.
And how many worlds will die...
if you get out?
Not yours.
She'll never know.
Don't you want
to see your daughter again?
I can't let you leave.
Why do you think you can stop me?
Give it to me, Janet.
Give it to me!
I couldn't beat him.
He was too powerful.
What did you do?
I'm sorry, Hope.
No!
I blew up his core.
Cut him off from time.
And trapped us both
down here forever.
But I gave him back enough.
Now that he had his suit back,
he became what he always was.
A conqueror.
He's got weapons and technology
centuries beyond anything
we can dream of.
He took his prison
and made it his empire.
I spent years fighting him,
running from him,
hiding from him.
And then you saved me.
You brought me home.
But I didn't deserve it.
I unleashed a monster on this place
and ran away.
Janet, you couldn't have known.
I'm sorry I never told you.
I just wanted to forget.
I just wanted to be your mom again.
I'm so sorry you had to
go through all of that alone.
But you are not alone now.
We'll stop him together.
He's after the core.
But he needs Pym Particles to reach it.
And if he's got Scott and Cassie,
he's got Pym Particles.
And a head start.
Exactly.
- We gotta get out of here.
- Hope.
He cannot get out.
You're an interesting man...
Scott Lang.
Um, I don't know who you are,
but you've made a big mistake.
Okay?
I'm an Avenger.
I've called the other Avengers...
You're an Avenger?
Have I killed you before?
What?
They all blur together after a while.
You're not the one with the hammer?
No, that's Thor.
We get confused a lot.
Similar body types.
Who are you?
Just a man
who's lost a lot of time.
Like you.
But we can help each other with that.
M.O.D.O.K. tells me you're a good thief.
Yeah, he stole something from me.
Do not speak when I am in the room.
Gotta say, Janet was a lot more helpful.
You know Janet too?
Does everyone down here know Janet?
She didn't tell you about me?
I guess that's not a surprise.
Janet stole something from me.
My ticket out of here.
And you're the only one
who can steal it back.
And why would I do that?
Because you want to get out of here.
And I need to get out of here.
Because I know how it ends.
How what ends?
All of it.
I don't live in a straight line.
And with time,
it's hard
not to skip to the end.
So, if you want to stop what's coming,
and trust me,
you do...
I am the only shot you have.
What's coming?
Me.
A lot of me.
They exiled me, down here.
They're afraid of me.
But I'm the man who can get you home.
So,
do we have a deal?
No, I don't think we do.
Dad!
Let me make this easy for you.
You will bring me what I need
or I will kill your daughter
in front of you,
then make you relive that moment
over and over again in time, endlessly,
until you beg me to kill you.
Do we understand?
Don't do this.
I'm a man who likes to be understood.
Dad.
Don't listen to him.
No! No!
Look, we can talk about this.
Don't do it!
You really should do it.
Please.
That's my daughter, please.
Do you want her to live,
or do you want her to die?
Please!
You think I'm lying?
Do I look like a liar to you?
Stop!
Dad!
I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'll do it.
Just let her go.
Let her go.
Let her go!
You're out of your league.
Ant-Man.
Just be glad I need you.
Don't touch her again.
Then give me what I need.
Where is it?
What is that?
It was a multiversal engine core.
A power source that can take you
anywhere in space and time.
Then Janet blew it up.
It's in that?
It is that.
And we have to get to the center.
That's good to know.
You'll have to shrink down
and pass through the eye of the storm.
Once you're inside, find the core
and size it back down.
What does it look like?
When I steal something,
I usually know what I'm stealing.
You'll know it when you see it.
Get in and out as fast as you can.
The longer you're in there,
the more your mind will come undone.
Better hurry.
Dad!
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
I messed up.
Cassie.
My whole life happened
because I messed up.
The only thing I didn't mess up is you.
Dad!
It's okay.
I love you, Peanut.
I love you too.
Okay.
I'm in.
Darren, can you hear me?
Darren?
M.O.D.O.K., can you hear me?
What?
- I'm in.
- Okay.
Okay, so what do I do?
What's the plan?
Don't die?
Thanks.
Big help, M.O.D.O.K.
Do you see it?
Yeah.
I see it.
I'm heading in.
Whoa!
What the hell?
I told you, Scott.
Getting in was just the beginning.
You never said that.
Why am I looking at another me?
I'm not another me.
You're another me.
You just came out...
Why am I looking at another me?
You're looking at the
possibility of another you.
You're in a Probability Storm.
What does any of that mean?
You don't know?
Why would I know?
Because you got me in here.
Oh, so, I am the real one, huh?
No.
I didn't say that.
What the hell?
Wait. Wait, wait.
What is this place?
It's a Probability Storm.
Every choice you could make,
existing all at once.
What is he saying?
What's he saying?
You're inside Schrodinger's box.
And you're the cat.
That doesn't make sense.
Oh, I get it.
Nobody move! All right?
Nobody move!
Why should we listen to you?
You're not even the real one.
What the hell?
Am I real?
I am the real one!
What the hell?
What the hell.
I'm the real one.
Whoa, whoa, guys.
Hey, relax.
Take it easy.
Breathe.
We'll figure this out.
Together.
Who are you?
Why are you dressed like that?
Because I work at Baskin-Robbins.
This is my uniform.
These are normal clothes.
- Why are you dressed like that?
- Do you have ice cream?
Enough!
Let's do this!
Oh, we're all gonna die.
Wait.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait!
No!
No! Wait! No!
I've got a read on Scott.
Out of the way!
Mom! What is this?
What are you doing?
Don't look at them.
They're just possibilities.
They're not you.
Scott, where are you?
Why am I here?
Don't worry.
It'll work this time.
What are you...
Wait, wait, no, no. Stop.
Stop! No!
I got this, guys.
I got this!
I got it!
Scott, where are you?
Scott!
Where are you, Scott?
- I can't breathe.
- Ow, that's my neck.
Stop kicking me!
Help!
Oh, my back!
We're all gonna die!
Get off me!
Dad.
Come back.
Dad,
if you can hear me,
come back.
Just come back.
- Don't give up.
- Come on.
Dad, just come back...
Come on.
...one more time.
- She needs us.
- Please.
- Yes, come on.
- Come back.
She needs us.
Let's do it together.
Get him up! Get him up!
Grab him! Grab him!
Let's go.
Come on, lift him!
Yes!
I got ya, I got ya! Go.
Come on. That's it.
Come on!
Give him a boost!
Come on, we're doing it for Cassie!
Fellas, let's go!
Everyone together!
What are you doing?
How are you able to do that?
I'll tell you how.
We all want the same thing.
And I'm coming, Cassie.
Go get her, pal.
Everyone, let's go!
Come on!
Come on, closer.
Get him higher!
Hang on, guys, hang on.
Careful.
Steady, steady.
Steady.
That's it.
Let's go.
What?
No.
What happened? Did it work?
Sorry, buddy!
- No, no, no.
Hope, are you real?
I'm real.
Then let's do this.
You ready?
Ready.
Come on.
We gotta get that thing out of here.
No, no, no. Wait.
He's got Cassie.
- What?
- Scott.
Janet.
Give that to me.
We have to go now.
No.
He's got Cassie.
We will save her.
I promise you we will save her,
but you cannot give that to him.
I wouldn't trust her.
Janet has a way of...
changing her mind.
Hello, Jellybean.
So...
what's it gonna be, Scott?
Well, well.
If it isn't my old mentor.
Hi, Hank.
Darren?
Didn't expect to see
your protege again after all...
Holy shit, Darren.
What happened to you?
I'm the ultimate weapon!
Do I need to take it?
Where is my daughter?
Scott.
Don't.
We had a deal.
She'll be fine without you.
So long, Hank.
Henry.
You left me right here to die.
Let's see how they do.
What did you see?
We didn't really get a chance
to talk about it last time.
But I always wondered.
When you touched my mind...
what did you see?
A monster
who thinks he's a god.
When you can see time the way I do,
you don't get to close your eyes.
And you're the only one who sees?
I am the only one
that can see it's broken.
And who broke it?
I did.
Every version of me.
My variants.
Throughout the Multiverse.
Playing with time,
like children.
But I saw how it ends.
I saw their chaos
spreading across realities.
Universes colliding.
Endless incursions.
I saw the Multiverse.
And it was dying.
All because of them.
So, I took control.
You mean you started a war.
And now you wanna wipe away
any universe that's a threat to you.
That's what monsters do.
That's what conquerors do.
They burn the broken world.
And they make a new one.
You don't care about saving
anything or anyone.
You only want revenge
because they beat you.
Because you lost.
I have lost.
You have no idea what I have lost.
And I will burn them out of time
for what they've done to me.
You'll be wiping out entire timelines.
Murdering trillions of people.
I wish that mattered, Janet.
Oh, God.
What am I doing?
What?
Hank!
Are these your ants?
From the ant farm?
Yes, Scott, they're my ants.
How did you find them down here?
I've been picking up strange
signals ever since we crashed.
First I thought
maybe it was a malfunction.
Some kind of interference.
What is that?
But it wasn't.
It was the ants.
They were reaching out the whole time.
Apparently, they passed through
some sort of time dilation.
They've lived thousands
of years in a single day,
expanding their knowledge,
their science,
becoming more advanced
than I could have ever thought.
I didn't find them.
They found me.
I told you they were smart.
They've already built something
of a technocratic Class-Two civilization.
I mean, I know socialism
is a charged word,
but we could learn a lot from these...
Dad.
Yeah, they're my ants.
And ants don't give up.
I don't care who this guy is.
I don't care what he can do.
I'm getting Cassie.
So, how do we even the odds against Kang?
We've got some ideas.
What are you thinking?
Well, as a great writer once said,
"There's always room to grow."
You read my book?
Every goddamn word.
Come on.
Let's go to work.
Hey! I'm sorry.
That was probably terrifying.
What are you doing here?
I'm rescuing you.
How?
That's a good question.
Does this thing have like a key?
Or a card? Like a room key?
Do you know, like a...
Shit!
Jump and tap.
Jentorra.
I'm sorry I got your people hurt.
How can I help?
Wow.
Let's hurt 'em back.
Damn, you're cool.
Do you have a plan?
Freeing you was basically my plan.
We need to get a message out
to anyone who can still fight.
Then free our people
from the detention cells below
and launch a counteroffensive from within.
Yeah, you have a plan.
So, how do we get a message out?
Follow me.
Okay. Great.
I built an empire down here, Janet.
And I'm taking it with me.
You really should've let me out
when you had the chance.
History is not written.
It is forged.
Today, we ascend.
From this fortress,
I will take my revenge
on those who banished me.
Today we conquer eternity.
And the dynasty of Kang shall...
Hello?
Is this working?
Cassie?
I can't tell if this is working.
Okay.
I think we're on.
I'll hold them off.
Get the message out.
I thought you were getting
the message out.
Now!
We're inside.
We breached the tower.
And I'm with Jentorra.
He's not invincible.
I know it might feel like
it's too late,
like all we do is just lose.
But the family I've lost
taught me to keep fighting.
And if they were here,
they would too.
We need to look out
for the little guy.
My dad taught me that.
'Cause when people needed help,
he didn't look the other way.
And neither do we.
We need to move!
Come to the tower!
Fight back!
I know you've been waiting.
Now is the time to strike.
He knows he can't take all of us.
Come to the...
Cassie.
I think I found the signal.
Mom's gotta be there, too.
Let's go.
I'll drive.
Find Lang's daughter.
Kill her.
Let's go. Let's go!
If you want to fight, follow me!
It's over, Cassie.
Free the others. Go!
He's gonna see us coming.
Yeah.
I'll make sure of it.
Begin the launch.
Your dad's not here, Cassie,
but I guess that's not a big surprise.
Kang!
We had a deal.
You took my daughter!
Holy shit.
That's big.
You lied to me!
Our word is our bond.
Without that, we're nothing!
- Bring him down.
- Yes, sir.
Keep going.
I've got them.
Yeah, come on!
There's so many!
Scott!
I can't hold them!
They came.
Way to go, Cassie!
Yes!
Come on! Let's go!
Revolution!
Burn it all down.
Fight!
Cover!
Get down!
What is the bridge code?
I'll die first.
One-eight-one-four-seven.
Damn!
You'll need this.
Hi.
This is our home!
Let's take it back!
No!
I have holes.
I have holes!
I didn't know he could do that.
Kang!
Where is she?
Launch now!
Whoa.
What is that?
He's getting out.
Oh, no, he's not.
Keep him away from the rings.
Whoa! Dad!
Dad, I'm coming!
Dad!
Nowhere left to run.
Please let this work.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Let's go.
You think this is over?
Come on! Let's go.
Darren, just stop
trying to be whatever this is.
I don't know what to be.
Tell me what to be.
I don't know.
Just don't be a dick.
It's too late.
Look at me.
I'm such a dick.
It's never too late to stop being a dick.
We've gotta stop him.
I have an idea.
Ready?
Probably not.
One, two, three. Now!
Dad!
Cassie?
You're huge.
I'm huge.
I love you, Peanut.
I love you too.
I'm so proud of you.
I feel like I'm hugging Godzilla.
I know.
It feels so cool.
I know, right?
I'm so hungry.
Yeah, that happens.
I could eat everything.
Everything. I know.
But I really want like a lime.
Right?
Citrus. It's weird. I know.
Citrus.
It's...
Take the tower!
It's over.
You still can't see it.
It's never over.
We have to go, right now.
No.
Come on.
No!
I know, I know,
but we have to go.
- No!
- Come on.
You son of a...
- Oh, God.
- Scott.
Come on.
You think this is new to me?
Do you know how many
rebellions I have put down?
No, no, no, no, no.
How many worlds I've conquered?
How many Avengers I've killed?
And you think you can beat me?
I am Kang!
You...
You talk to ants.
My name is Darren,
and I am not a dick!
Sorry I'm late.
Lotta ants.
Oh, is this you?
Maybe you were right about me, Cassie.
Darren.
Are you okay?
Probably not.
Darren?
Hi, Hope.
You changed your hair.
What the hell happened?
Yeah.
No, it's...
It's a whole thing.
I'll tell you later.
That was... I...
I don't know what to say.
Thanks, Scott.
You always were a brother to me.
I was?
I was.
And at least I died
an Avenger.
Yeah.
You did.
Yeah. No, it's...
You're in.
A lot has happened today.
Henry?
Janet?
- Mom, where are you?
- I'm in the tower.
I think I can give us one shot back.
But we don't have much time.
If we wanna go home...
we have to go now.
We'll finish this.
Thank you.
Oh, wow!
Come on!
Let's go!
All right.
Good luck.
Come on.
Thanks, buddy.
You did it.
Let's go home.
Where's Scott?
He was right behind me.
You should've looked the other way.
Yeah, well,
never been great at that.
And you're not getting out.
I want you to remember.
You could've gone home.
You could've seen your daughter again.
But you thought you could win.
I don't have to win.
We both just have to lose.
Dad!
Where...
Where is she?
Is she...
No, she's okay.
Where is she?
She's okay.
She's okay. She's okay.
Scott, they're all okay.
She's safe?
They're all okay.
You did it.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
No, no, no.
No, don't let go.
Don't let go.
Don't ever let go.
I got you.
You came back.
I love you, Hope.
I love you, Scott.
Let's go home.
Home's good.
My life doesn't make sense.
I used to ask myself
a lot of questions about that.
Ah.
"Scott you just saved
"the Quantum Realm with your family
"and drank a guy without holes.
"Why does this kind of stuff
keep happening to you?
"That doesn't make any sense."
But you know what?
Who said life has to make sense?
Rubin!
You are the bug!
I was wrong. Yeah.
You are the other bug.
You're the bug man.
You get big and get small like a big bug!
You're right. That's me.
Just a coffee, please.
Twelve dollar.
Oh.
Twelve!
I used to wonder if this
chapter in my life was over,
but as Cassie reminded me,
"There's always someone you can help."
Came out of cake making
retirement for you.
Wow.
You... You made this yourself?
Yeah! I don't usually make the cakes.
I know.
This is the first one
I've made since 1997.
You're a real artist.
It's been a pretty wild ride.
One day you're fired
from Baskin-Robbins,
the next you're beating
a time-traveling space king.
We did beat him, right?
I mean, yeah,
that's what happened.
He... He was getting out
and he didn't get out.
I think.
But he also said
something bad was coming
and that everyone would die
if he didn't get out.
Wait.
So, did I just kill everyone?
Is everyone gonna die
because of me?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my... What did I do?
What... What did...
What did I do?
You know what?
It's probably fine.
Like I said,
life doesn't make any sense,
so maybe stop asking
so many questions, Scott.
Stop overthinking it.
Surprise!
Happy Birthday to you
It's not my birthday.
I know.
But I missed a few.
This is good.
We're all together.
You're fine.
Everything's probably fine.
Kang's gone.
You did it.
Don't have to worry
about that guy anymore.
Ah.
Thanks.
Happy fake birthday, Cassie.
Oh.
So, the exiled one is dead.
You sure he's dead?
If it wasn't true,
I wouldn't call you.
Must really eat you up,
that you're not the one who killed him.
None of us
killed him.
They did.
They're beginning to touch the Multiverse.
And if we let them,
they will take...
everything
we've built.
So let's stop wasting time.
We're late.
How many did you call?
All of us.
Time is everything.
It shapes our lives.
But, perhaps, we can shape...
...it.
It's him.
What?
You made him sound
like this terrifying figure.
He is.
Modify by Blue-Bird™